<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="default.xsl"?>
<fr:tree
toc="true"
numbered="true"
show-heading="true"
show-metadata="true"
expanded="true"
root="true"
xmlns:fr="http://www.jonmsterling.com/jms-005P.xml"><fr:frontmatter><fr:anchor>249</fr:anchor><fr:addr
type="user">main</fr:addr><fr:route>index.xml</fr:route><fr:title
text="Patrick Nicodemus">Patrick Nicodemus</fr:title><fr:authors /></fr:frontmatter><fr:mainmatter><fr:p>Hello, and welcome to my personal website.</fr:p><fr:p>I am a research mathematician interested in applied topology, category theory, homological algebra, type theory and formal verification.</fr:p><fr:p>At the moment, I primarily work on applied topology, in the <fr:link
type="external"
href="https://camara-lab.org/">Cámara Lab</fr:link> at the University of Pennsylvania. Specifically, I apply the <fr:link
type="external"
href="https://media.adelaide.edu.au/acvt/Publications/2011/2011-Gromov%E2%80%93Wasserstein%20Distances%20and%20the%20Metric%20Approach%20to%20Object%20Matching.pdf">Gromov-Wasserstein distance</fr:link> to the study of cell morphology. I also maintain <fr:link
type="external"
href="https://github.com/CamaraLab/CAJAL">CAJAL</fr:link>, a Python package for the analysis of cell morphology.</fr:p><fr:p>This website is under construction. Over the course of the next few weeks, I intend to start blogging here and uploading content, ideally, both my about my mathematics research, and potentially some literate formal verification using the Rocq theorem prover.</fr:p><fr:p>Some things you might find interesting:
<fr:ul><fr:li>Some nice looking Rocq proofs:
       <fr:ul><fr:li><fr:link
type="external"
href="./MyTheory.html/MyTheory.A.html">Webpage aesthetics</fr:link>, i.e. basic use of LaTeX and Coqdoc.</fr:li></fr:ul>
          <fr:li><fr:link
type="external"
href="./MyTheory.html/MyTheory.nat_example.html">Brief walkthrough</fr:link> of Rocq's dependent pattern matching, illustrated via natural number arithmetic. No use of tactics.</fr:li>
          <fr:li><fr:link
type="external"
href="./MyTheory.html/MyTheory.eq_example.html">Walkthrough continued</fr:link>, this time focusing on basic properties of equality. No use of tactics.</fr:li>
          <fr:li><fr:link
type="external"
href="./MyTheory.html/MyTheory.elpi_exploration.html">Some practice with Elpi</fr:link>, a logic programming language which Enrico Tassi and others have been developing as a tactic language for the Rocq theorem prover.</fr:li></fr:li></fr:ul></fr:p></fr:mainmatter><fr:backmatter /></fr:tree>